Towing the line
Seguindo a norma
I watched the host drink all the wine
Vi a anfitriã a beber o vinho todo
And now she rambles
E agora perde-se
Through the who and who have not
A falar de fulano e de sicrano
The old man is a painter
O velho é pintor
Of tired seascapes titled ‘Adventure’
De cansadas paisagens marítimas intituladas ‘Aventura’
So my mind wanders picking at the table to cure the rot
E a minha mente divaga à pesca de algo para não apodrecer
Like a bird in a world with no trees
Como um pássaro num mundo sem árvores
You were hung up there in your disbelief
Lá estavas pendurada sem acreditar
I know I'm a hard rock to drag around
Sei que sou uma rocha difícil de acarretar
Love is in the early mornings
O amor é de manhã cedo
In the shadows under the trees
Nas sombras debaixo das árvores
Not in the cuckolded ashes
Não nas cinzas traiçoeiras
Floating down from the rookery
A flutuar pelo ninho abaixo
Down here, I’ll crow for you
Cá em baixo, cacarejo para ti
You crow for me
E tu para mim
Down here, I’ll crow for you
Cá em baixo, cacarejo para ti
You crow for me
E tu para mim
Towing the line
Seguindo a norma
I watched the host drink all the wine
Vi a anfitriã a beber o vinho todo
And now I’m purring for a drop of anything
E agora faço ronrom à espera que caia algo
Throwing stones at your window
Lanço pedras à tua janela
You turn to me as if it’s simple
Tu olhas-me como se fosse simples
Why can’t you be like the blackbird
Não sabes ser como o melro
And sing
E cantar
I say I’m the westerlies in Ireland
Eu digo que sou os ventos do oeste
So decadent and violent
Tão decadentes e violentos
Can’t you see I’m a forager
Não vês que sou um predador
Clawing at the bedrock
A arranhar a base da rocha
Love is in the early mornings
O amor é de manhã cedo
In the shadows under the trees
Nas sombras debaixo das árvores
Not in the cuckolded ashes
Não nas cinzas traiçoeiras
Floating down from the rookery
A flutuar pelo ninho abaixo
Down here, I’ll crow for you
Cá em baixo, cacarejo para ti
You crow for me
E tu para mim
Down here, I’ll crow for you
Cá em baixo, cacarejo para ti
You crow for me
E tu para mim